Narrator: in
countries and cities
Speaker: in Spain, in Madrid
Narrator: rooms
Speaker: in the kitchen
Narrator: buildings
Speaker: in a shop
in a museum
Narrator: closed spaces
Speaker: in a park
in a garden
in a car
Narrator: months
Speaker: in February
in June
Narrator: seasons
Speaker: in winter
Narrator: years
Speaker: in twenty twenty-five
Narrator: times of day
Speaker: in the morning
in the afternoon
in the evening
Narrator: on
transport
Speaker: on a bike
on a bus
on a train
on a plane
on a ship
Narrator: a surface
Speaker: on the floor
on a table
on a shelf
on the balcony
on the roof
on the wall
Narrator: dates
Speaker: on the first of March
Narrator: days
Speaker: on Tuesday
on New Year’s Day
on Valentine’s Day
Narrator: at
places
Speaker: at school
at home
at work
at university
at the airport
at the station
at a bus stop
at a party
at the door
Narrator: times
Speaker: at six o’clock
at half past two
at quarter to eight
at night
at the weekend
Narrator: festival periods
Speaker: at Christmas
at Easter